The Peach-Black 5, the Battle of Concentration with Renni Takagi
Now the four members of Peach Black Clover Z will compete in a variety of events and predict the order of finish in the second race, the Peach Black 5.
Well, you see, for that horse, for Jackie, and for Jokey...
Jokey!
For Jokey, too, a race is about concentration, isn't it?
Some of us don't have that kind of concentration, but I'd say we're all pretty good at it.
I'm a short-term type.
We're short-term, focused people.
We can't sustain it, but we can concentrate for a moment.
Everyone can.
I think we've already passed the top five.
The first to start off in unison is Nanako Momotaka in the red hat, second is Tamashiro in the yellow hat, Ayaka Sasaki in the pink hat is in the middle, and Renni Takagi in the purple hat is in the last row.
They will be in the top row of the idols.
me
This time, you'll have to concentrate on a very easy task if you have the concentration to complete it.
You will get one point for clearing the first one, and finally, we will decide the ranking by the points you get for doing several battles.
First of all, the first battle will be "Ippatsu Nose" by the prefecture.
I'm good at this sometimes, but I'll take this one too, so I'll take this one, thank you very much.
The challenge from Tamaishi
Which one do you like?
What are you talking about?
Okay, I'll take it.
Then, Mr. Tamai, please give me a shot.
I'm getting nervous.
My hips are in disarray.
I can do it.
It didn't work.
I didn't expect it.
It's more of a failure than a boulder.
Failure.
Can I try again with a casual heart?
Can't do it.
Concentration.
Kanako Momota's challenge
Here we go.
I don't get it.
Failure!
Failed!
Ayaka Sasaki's challenge
Here we go!
Ah, it was played... Failure.
Surprisingly, it doesn't go well.
Ah, I'm bounced off! Fail!
Renni Takagi's challenge
Go for it!
Oh, no...
Rei didn't even scratch it.
I'm really bad at Senkama.
I'm really bad at it.
It's so frustrating, isn't it?
Next time.
Next up, 10 cups stacked on top of each other.
You have to stack 10 cups vertically within 45 seconds.
We're going to do this one outside.
It's too bright and hot, so let's do it inside.
That's the most rational way.
But you've got to put yourself in the jockey's shoes.
The wind is not always on our side.
You're all going to run with the wind, and when the gate opens, it'll be a split-second race.
The four members of the Peach-colored Clover Z are ready to take on the challenge.
Let's get ready to go!
Here we go... the wind's picking up, and we're flying.
Takagi's doing well, and Tamai's doing well.
And Momota's behind... and Sasaki's on his fourth.
Takagi's on his fifth one, and the wind's picking up.
Momota's lighting up! And Whisaki!
Momota lights up and then the whisper!
It's a little unsteady, isn't it?
Takagi's a little unsteady.
He's holding it down, he's holding it down, how's Tamai?
Tamai, you're stabilizing, too, but time is running out.
less than 10 seconds left... how about it... how about it... we'll clear 10!
I'd like to clear ten of them!
Tamai clear cup!
Tamai is the only one who has cleared 10 pieces!
Momota lights up
The next competition was to grab the bridge with a single shot of a peanut!The next competition is the "Bean Grab"!
You have to move 10 beans to another plate within 30 seconds with chopsticks.
I've done this before with a regular bridge, but never with chopsticks.
It's a little long.
The four members of the Peach-Colored Clover Z are going to try it all at once.
Now, please concentrate.
Even before you hold the bridge.
It's tough.
Why don't you show us?
Don't show me.
This one second is tough.
Only Mr. Takagi doesn't kneel.
They're chopsticks.
They're long.
Now let's get started.
Get in position and start preparing.
Delicate work is required.
Concentrate!
Takagi, standing, doing well.
And Tamai is doing well.
Momota, one porter for Taus.
Also doing well!
Sasaki, still on the first one!
Takagi, you're halfway clear!
Tamai's a little out of place.
And Momota... quietly.
Everyone's silent.
We've got less than 10 seconds left in silence.
I'm hoping we can make it 10 seconds.
Sasaki is catching up here.
Takagi leads!
And there's 3.2 seconds left!
Momota is clear!
Sasaki also clears just in time.
Tamai failed to clear.
Only three cleared!
They're catching up! They're catching up!
Just in time!
Mr. Sasaki was really close to his time!
It was so close!
He was behind in the first half of the race.
But he did a great job to catch up.
Amazing!
And Momota, you also kept quiet.
At first, he had a hard time
Grabbing with these chopsticks.
Mr. Takagi was the first to get in!
The whole thing went well.
Was it good to do it standing up?
I think it was good to do it standing up.
I think the angle was good, too.
You were very steady.
And surprisingly, Mr. Tamai...
I went in a little bit once.
But it just popped out.
My parents took care of that.
My parents thought I had to go back in.
So we switched to that, and it was pretty frustrating.
You caught up, didn't you?
I thought I was doing pretty well.
It was so close.
We caught up. We caught up.
So, Momota, Sasaki and Takagi...
got one point each!
Next up was the Rubik's Cube!
I'm sure everyone is familiar with this one.
You have to get one side of the cube within 30 seconds.
30 seconds sounds difficult!
Even though it's only one side...
But still... it's hard!
I wonder how fast people can do it.
Some people can do it all, right?
There are people who can do the whole thing in 30 seconds.
The four members of Peach Color Clover Z tried it all at once.
Let's get started.
First up is Sasaki.
She's staring at us with a worried look on her face.
Move it slowly
Rotate
Spinning with a handshakeKuru Kuru with a handshake
And this is Momota
This one looks anxious too
He's peeking in
He hasn't moved it yet.
How's Takagi?
I'm guessing yellow...
Or maybe he's set it to blue.
And Tamai...
And Tamai? He's going to use his own colors?
And Momota?
Five seconds left on the clock.
Here it comes! Tamai, you're clear!
Yellow, clear!
And how about Momota?
We're done here!
They're all here!
Why?
And it's clear on yellow.
Why? It's not working?
I don't know what color I'm supposed to get.
I was going for blue.
I was going for orange.
But orange wasn't even halfway there.
Then green came around.
Talking to myself.
The camera's rolling.
I'm not saying that.
You've been talking to yourself the whole time.
I'm at full strength.
I can't do this.
I'm home.
Next time...
How about Momota?
The next game...
Stick Catching Game
A stick is dropped into the open palm of the hand, and the question is whether the player can catch it or not.
It's a simple and clear game.
It's so simple and straightforward that we'll bring it all to you at once.
Paint?
It's thin.
Catch and clear!
That's thin.
Catch clear.
Here you go.
Catch.
Over.
Mr. Cannon, I don't like the way you're moving.
Look.
No, I won't look.
I won't look.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Clear!
Mr. Sasaki cleared just in time!
I can't see him!
Clear!
Mr. Sasaki is clear, just in time.
Are you sure you want your hands in that position?
Yes, sir.
No?
It feels a little off.
Failure.
Failed.
It feels a little off.
Failure.
Failed.
Trash can shot
You do this a lot in your daily life, don't you?
We do it all the time.
Throw, right?
Throw it.
We work out everyday, don't we?
I don't do it often.
You grew up with it?
I don't.
I don't do it.
No, no, no, I've seen it.
You haven't.I've never seen you do it.
I've seen you take something off.
I've seen you miss a lot.
Cobblestone challenge
Underthrow.
Missed.
Kanako Momota's Challenge
Wow, it's tough, tough, tough.
Distance
I don't know the distance.
Check the position of the feet
Underthrow right hand
Missed.
Right hand underthrow.
Ayaka Sasaki's challenge
Here we go.
Ahhh...
That's too close.
She must have put a lot of effort into it.
Missed it by a long shot.
Ahhh...
Almost!
The challenge of Renni Takagi
Too short!
Failure!
A little too short.
A little this way.
A little off to the left.
Too short.
Failed.
Tissue disposable chopstick grasping
Tissue chopstick grab!
Yay!
What's this?
Mr. Takagi drops a tissue from a high place.
Can the other members catch the tissue with the disposable chopsticks?
Looks like they can!
It's Mr. Takagi's turn.
This is no longer an outdoor event.
There are too many colds!
It's more of a boulder challenge.
I'll never do it.
I will never do it.
Never do it
We'll never do it.
It's going downhill fast.
Look, look, look.
How did that happen?
It's funny.
Mr. Takagi, please.
One, two, three.
Catchy.
Yay!
Ike
Kako Momota's challenge
Excuse me, Mr. Camera, but I'm going to put it on your butt.
You're calling for a cold!
Mr. Takagi!
Yes, sir.
I'll be counting on you today.
All right!
We're clear!
Everyone's doing well.
Surprisingly...
No problem.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ayaka Sasaki's challenge
Okay.
Okay, I'm concentrating.
I don't have a cold right now.
Okay, I'm coming.
Let's go now.
Come on, please.
Here we go.
Okay.
Oh, it flew away!Oh, it flew away, it flew away.
At least for now...
Yay!
Reine Takagi's challenge
Ready?
Let's catch!
Get points!
Okay!
Let's announce the points
Tamai-san has 4 points
Mr. Momota and Mr. Sasaki have 3 points
Mr. Takagi has 2 points
Mr. Tamai won with 4 points
Thank you very much!
Congratulations!
I knew it!
You're so strong!
Looking back, how do you feel, Ms. Tamai?
Yes, I think so.
There were some things...
I wasn't in my element at times.
But I think I was able to achieve a good overall balance.
I think we had a good match.
This competition will continue.
Yes, sir.
Good luck next time.
And for those of you who are watching, were your predictions correct?
Did you guess right?
If you guessed that Mr. Tamai won the race, you were right.
Maybe you could have guessed it.
Maybe I could have guessed it.
It turned out a bit as expected.
Unpine.
What a pity.
And so, the Peach and Black 5 game continues!
That's all for today's second round.
Thank you very much.
Why don't you enjoy the Spring Tennou-sho this weekend?
Next time notice